{
    "subject": "resource/Marcus_Rose",
    "predicate": "ontology/university",
    "object": "resource/Magdalene_College,_Cambridge",
    "human_readable": "Marcus Rose attended Magdalene College, Cambridge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9400147795677185,
            "question": "What might Marcus Rose have studied at Magdalene College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8688629865646362,
            "question": "Where did Marcus Rose attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8440395593643188,
            "question": "What is the name of the college Marcus Rose attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103792667388916,
            "question": "Is Marcus Rose affiliated with Cambridge University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7225561141967773,
            "question": "Did Marcus Rose study at a college in England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6178674101829529,
            "question": "What is the significance of attending Magdalene College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5574169158935547,
            "question": "What type of institution is Magdalene College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5380191206932068,
            "question": "Is Magdalene College a well-known institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.474117636680603,
            "question": "Are there any famous alumni from Magdalene College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3768528699874878,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Marcus Rose's education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marcus Rose attended Magdalene College, Cambridge.",
            "html": "dbpedia_430_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous alumni from Magdalene College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_430_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Magdalene College a well-known institution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_430_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of institution is Magdalene College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_430_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_430_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. Specifically, the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_430/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt` mentions that Marcus Rose was educated at Magdalene College, Cambridge University."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Marcus Rose was educated at Magdalene College, Cambridge University, which supports the statement that Marcus Rose attended Magdalene College, Cambridge."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}